One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Which one of you is Arlong?!
أيُّكم أرلونغ؟
My name happens to be Arlong.
...لعلّ أرلونغ هو اسمي
I'm Luffy.
أنا لوفي
Luffy?
لوفي؟
And what are you, exactly?
من تكون إذًا؟
A pirate!
!قرصان
Hey, hold up, you bastard.
انتظر يا هذا
Where do you think you're goin'?
إلى أين تمضي بظنِّك؟
You need to run things by us first, kiddo.
عليك إخبارنا أولًا يا فتى
Hey, now!
!هيَّا أخبرنا
If you don't stop...
...إلَّم تتوقف
Move!
تنحَّيا
What does a pirate want with me?
ما حاجةُ قرصانٍ مني؟
Just who the hell are you?!
من تكون بالضبط؟
Luffy...
...لوفي
Help me...
...ساعدني
I won't let you make our navigator cry!
!إياك أن تُبكي ملاحتنا
Why, you...
!أيها الوغد
How dare you insult Arlong!
كيف لك أن تشتم أرلونغ-سان؟
Butt out, shrimp!
!لا تتدخَّلوا أيتها الأسماك الصغيرة
Sheesh...
...ويحك
You just had to run ahead by yourself...
!تقدَّمت وحيدًا غير مبالٍ
I can handle myself just fine.
ليس وكأني سأخسر وحدي
Idiot! When did I say I was worried about you?!
متى قلت أنني قلقٌ بشأنك يا أحمق؟
I just don't want you hogging all the fun.
لا أرغب في أن تأخذ كل الفرائس لك وحدك
Oh, makes sense!
هكذا إذًا
W-Well, I don't mind letting you hog it all!
أ-أمَّا أنا فلا أمانع أن تأخذهم لك وحدك
How awfully generous of you.
أنت جريءٌ حقًّا
That's the guy! The mysterious swordsman!
ذاك هو، إنه السيَّاف المجهول
That's Roronoa Zoro.
إنه رورونوا زورو
Yeah? Yeah, I thought so! He tricked me!
أجل، كما توقعت
He really took me for a ride...
...استغلّني وركب معي
No, wait... Didn't I give him a ride?
لا، ألم أكن من أوصله؟
Look! It's that long-nosed guy!
انظروا، إنه صاحب الأنف الطويل
D-Didn't Nami kill him?!
أ-ألم تقتله نامي؟
It's just as I suspected, then.
كما توقعت بالضبط
The girl turned against us!
!خانتنا تلك المرأة
Hey! Who are those guys?!
من يكونون يا جماعة؟
– Hold it!
تمهّلوا
He sent Arlong flying!
!طيَّرَ أرلونغ ذاك
Unbelievable!
!غير معقول
No ordinary human could do that!
!ما هي بأفاعيل بشرية
They're...
...إنهم
Do you still want to try and break in now?
أما زلتم تريدون اقتحام المكان؟
In a fight like this, there's nothing you guys can do.
!بتدخلكم لن تصبح المعركة إلا أقل متعةً
You'll only get in their way!
!ستعترضون طريقهم فحسب
B-But... why are they fighting?
لـ-لكن... لماذا يقاتلون؟
What reason do they have to fight?!
ما الغاية التي تدفعهم لذلك؟
What reason?
الغاية؟
Big Sis Nami was crying!
!كانت أختي الكبيرة نامي تبكي
What other reason do they need to put their lives on the line?
أهم بحاجةٍ لأكثر من هذا ليضعوا أنفسهم في عداد الموت؟
A pirate, huh? I see...
...قرصانٌ إذًا؟ فهمت
So that's what this is about.
هذه رابطتكم إذًا
You were after Nami from the very start.
كنتم تستهدفون نامي منذ البداية
But really...
...لكن
what can you four lowbred worms possibly do?!
ماذا بوسعكم فعله أيتها الديدان الأربعة؟
Fools! You're not worth Arlong's time!
!لا تستحقون وقت أرلونغ-سان الثمين يا حمقى
I know just the guy to take you on!
!سيَفي ذاك بالغرض
Don't tell me...
...أيعقل
It's coming!
إنه قادم
Wh-Wh-Wh-What's going on?!
ما-ما-ما-ماذا يجري؟
Rise, Momoo!
اخرج يا مومو
A-A monster!
!و-وحش
That's the monster from the Grand Line that destroyed Gosa!
إنه وحش الغراند لاين الذي دمَّر قرية غوسا
It's here!
!خرج
Th-That's...
...ذ-ذلك
...the fearsome Momoo!
!بقرة البحر مومو
Oh, that guy?
أيعنون هذا؟
He's with the fishmen?
تبيَّن أنه رفيقٌ للبرمائيين
Wait! Momoo! Where are you going?!
انتظر يا مومو، إلى أين تمضي؟
Hey! Stop! Get back here! Momoo!
تمهَّل وعُد إلى هنا يا مومو
Momoo. What do you think you're doing?
ماذا تفعل يا مومو؟
I mean, if you wanna run away, I won't stop you.
على كلٍّ، إن كنتَ تريد أن تهرب فلن أمنعك
Well, Momoo?
أفهمت يا مومو؟
Here it comes! Here it comes!
!إنه قادمٌ قادم
Alright!
حسنٌ
Follow Momoo!
فلتتبعوا مومو
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
اعذرني، اعذرني، اعذرني، اعذرني، اعذرني
I'll do it! This is a waste of time!
سأتكفَّل به، هذه مضيعة للوقت
What is he up to this time?!
ماذا دهاه؟
I've got a bad feeling about this...
...هذا يُريبني
His arms stretched!
!امتدَّت ذراعيه
Devil fruit powers?!
أهي قدرة فاكهة شيطان؟
What?!
ماذا؟
Who cares?!
غير مهم، لننطلق
Whoa! Run!
اهرب يا ولد
What? What's he doing?!
ماذا؟ ماذا يفعل؟
I dunno, but it doesn't look good!
لا أدري، لكني لا أراه أمرًا حسنًا
Gum-Gum...
فاكهة المطاط غومو غومو نو
Pinwheel!
المروحة كازاغوراما
I didn't come here to fight these guys!
لم آتِ إلى هنا لقتال هؤلاء الناس
If I'm gonna beat anyone up...
...من أريد أن أبطش به
it's gonna be you!
!هو أنت لا غيرك
What a coincidence...
...يا للمصادفة
I was just thinking about killing you, too.
وجدتني أفكر في قتلك أيضًا
That was dangerous, you moron!
كان ذلك خطيرًا يا وغد
Are you trying to kill us, too?!
أتنوي قتلنا أيضًا؟
Such destructive power...
...ما أشدَّها قوةً
I can't believe a human exists who can throw that giant beast!
لا يسعني تصديق وجودَ إنسانٍ يقوى رمي ذلك الوحش العملاق
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
أهذه المعركة من هذا العالم؟
How dare you hurt our brothers!
كيف تجرؤ إيذاء إخواننا؟
It seems like we're going to have to fight, too.
الظاهر إن علينا القتال أيضًا
Looks like we need to teach them the differences between our races.
أرى أن علينا تعليمهم مدى الاختلاف بين عرقيْنا
The real players are finally ready, huh?
ظهرت القوات الرئيسة أخيرًا
Please sit back and relax, Arlong.
يا أرلونغ-سان، ابقَ في مكانك مسترخيًا رجاءً
If you go on a rampage, you'll end up leveling Arlong Park.
إلَّم تتمالك نفسك ستُدمَّر أرلونغ بارك تمامًا
We'll take care of these guys!
!سنتكفَّل نحن بهم
Sure, do whatever you want.
طيِّب، افعلوا ما يحلو لكم
Hey. Guys. Hold on a second.
...اسمعا اسمعا، تمهَّلا قليلًا
That octopus is up to something.
ذاك الأخطبوط يخطِّط لشيءٍ
Octopus is best served sliced, salted, and boiled.
أفضل شرائح الأخطبوط تأتي مملحة ومسلوقة
Add some olive oil and paprika, and it pairs perfectly with a drink.
أضِف قليلًا من زيت الزيتون والفلفل الأحمر
Hey, I'm kinda in trouble here. Can I have a sec?
اسمعا، أنا في مأزق بسيط، أنصتا لي قليلًا
That's it! Kiss your sight goodbye!
خذوا قذيفة انعدام الرؤية هذه
Octohachi Black!
قذيفة حبر هاتشي تاكوهاتشي بلاك
You idiot! Why didn't you dodge?!
لِمَ لم تتفاداها أيها الأحمق؟
I can't see!
!ليس بوسعي الرؤية
Now to finish you off!
!وأما الآن لأجهزنَّ عليك
Hey, Luffy! Run!
اهرب يا لوفي
Y-Yeah... Th-That's the problem..
...حسنٌ، المشكلة أنَّ
I don't think I can run!
ليس بوسعي الحراك
M-My feet are stuck!
فـ-فساقاي عالقتان
You're the one who stuck them in the ground!
ألستَ من غرسهما في الأرض؟
Why is he always like this...?
...لِمَ عليه أن
Octohachi Black on the Rocks!
قذيفة حبر هاتشي في الصخور تاكوهاتشي بلاك أون ذا روكس
What a pain.
يا للإزعاج
Sanji! That was amazing!
!رائع، رائع يا سانجي
Seems like I chose one hell of an idiot for a captain.
أرى الحال انتهى بي لأتبع قبطانًا في غاية الحماقة
You said it.
أوافقك
He's... so cool!
إنه... مذهل
But he's a hundred times better than a bunch of thugs who'd hurt a lady.
لكنه يظلّ أفضل بمئة مرة من قراصنةٍ لُعناء يؤذون آنسة
Lady?
آنسة؟
Can't believe you'd break in here for one lousy girl.
لا يسعني تصور أنَّكم اقتحمتم المكان من أجل تلك المرأة الرذيلة
Lousy girl?
امرأة رذيلة؟
Just try and insult Nami one more time.
أهِن نامي-سان ثانيةً
I'll pan-fry you in butter and turn you into fishman meunière!
وسأستخدم مقلاةً بالزبدة لأحوّلك إلى مونيير برمائي
You seem somewhat skilled for a human.
أراك ماهر بالنسبة لبشري
But chivalry from a pirate is bound to be half-hearted.
أيُّ الشهامات تظلّ فاترة ما دامت نابعةً من قرصان
Go ahead and see if my chivalry is half-hearted or not.
أدعوك أن تختبر إن كانت شهامتي فاترةً أم لا
I spent half my life raised by a gristly old pirate.
تربّيتُ على يد قرصانٍ لا يُقهر لنصف حياتي
It appears you don't know the true power of the fishman race.
الظاهر إنَّك تجهل مستوى عرق البرمائيين الحق
No good. They're still pretty stuck.
لا جدوى، ما زالتا عالقتين تمامًا
Still?! They're still stuck?!
أ... أما زالتا عالقتين؟
Yep, still stuck.
نعم، ما زالتا عالقتين
I don't think pulling me is gonna get them unstuck.
أشعر أنَّ سحبي لن يحرّرهما من الأرض
Are you even trying?! Are you even trying to get your legs out?!
هل تحاول أساسًا؟ هل تحاول سحب ساقيك أساسًا؟
Who do they think they are, playing around in Arlong Park?!
ما بالهم يبعقون في أرلونغ بارك؟
I'll kill them!
!سأقتلهم
Come on, come on! Get unstuck already!
يا ولد، حرّر ساقيك سريعًا
Get back here!
عودا إلى هنا
Hey, octopus.
أيها الأخطبوط
They're busy right now.
إنهما مشغولان حاليًّا
I'll take you on.
سأواجهك أنا
Roronoa Zoro! That's right! I forgot!
!رورونوا زورو، ذكرتني
How dare you trick me!
كيف تجرأت خداعي؟
That's right! Not to mention all my brethren you cut down!
وحتى أنك مزّقتَ عديدًا من إخوتي
I don't care. That's all old news.
لستُ مهتمًّا بهذه الحكايا القديمة
It doesn't really matter why you want to kill me.
دافعك لقتلي غير مهم
The situation has changed.
فالأوضاع تغيرت
You're not trying to crush us anymore.
لستم من يحاولون القضاء علينا
We're trying to crush you!
بل نحن من نحاول القضاء عليكم
A-Alright, Zoro! The octopus is all yours! Nice!
حـ-حسنٌ يا زورو، لتتول أمر الأخطبوط، جميل
Luffy!
!لوفي
I'm back...
...عُدت
Why, you...
...أيها الوغد
My bad...
...اعذرني
Seems you really do want me to kill you.
الظاهر إنَّك تبتغي الموت حقًّا
Wasn't that the guy who saved Mr. Gen?
ألم يكن من أنقذ غين-سان؟
You're the people from Cocoyashi Village!
إنَّكم أهل قرية كوكوياشي
Judging from those weapons, I take it this is a rebellion?
نظرًا لأنكم مسلّحون جميعًا، هل أعدُّ هذا تمردًا؟
Then you're all–
...فإنَّكم جميعًا
Fire Star!
النجم المتفجر كاياكو بوشي
Big Bro Usopp!
!أخي الكبير أوسوب
You're dealing with me!
!إنَّ خصمك أنا
If you wanna die that badly, I'll finish you right now!
!ما دمت تبتغي الموت لهذه الدرجة فإليك إياه
Just who is that boy?
من ذاك الشاب؟
He's brave one minute, then runs away the next. He's a peculiar one...
إنَّه شجاعٌ تارةً وهاربٌ تارةً أخرى، عجيبٌ أمره
Get back here, big nose!
عُد يا ذا الأنف الطويل
You're one to talk, big mouth!
!إنَّك آخر من يتكلم يا ذا الفم الطويل
How are these guys pirates?
لِمَ هم قراصنة؟
You're all pathetic. Move. I can't watch another second of this.
إنَّكم مُثيرون للشفقة حقًّا، تنحّوا فقد سئمتُ مشاهدتكم
Arlong! We asked you not to go on a rampage!
ألم نطلب منك أن تتمالك نفسك يا أرلونغ-سان؟
I won't. I just thought up a fun game.
لن أفعل، إنَّما خطرت ببالي لعبة شيقة
I'm gonna kick...
!لأبطشنَّ بك
Do you seriously think you can beat us?
أتظنون أنَّ بوسعكم هزيمتنا حقًّا؟
So what if we do?
وماذا بذلك؟
We sure do, dummy!
سنهزمكم حقًّا يا أحمق، أفلت يدي
Sounds like he has something to say.
الظاهر إنَّ بجعبته كلام
What the...?! What the...?! What the...?!
ماذا... ماذا... ماذا؟
People with devil fruit powers can't swim!
أكلو فواكه الشيطان لا يستطيعون السباحة
Though, even people without powers would sink in this situation!
ولكن حتى غير آكليها سيغرقون في هذا الوضع
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
أيعقل أنه سيرميه للبحر؟
Gum-Gum Pistol!
فاكهة المطاط: المسدس غومو غومو نو: بيستول
Oww!
!مؤلم
Fool.
أيها الأحمق
Damn you!
أيها الوغد
How pointless.
لا فائدة
Luffy!
!لوفي
You bastard!
أيها الوغد
I'll save–
...أنا آتٍ لإنقاذ
Idiot! Don't get worked up!
لا تنفعل أيها الأحمق
They want us to go in the water!
غايتهم أن ننزل إلى الماء
Fishmen have the obvious advantage in an underwater fight!
فإنَّ البرمائيين يتمتعون بأفضلية واضحة في المعارك تحت المائية
There's only one way to save Luffy!
ثمَّة طريقة واحدة لإنقاذ لوفي
Take these guys down in a flash and hop in the water?
نهزمهما بسرعة ثمَّ ننزل إلى الماء؟
Let's do it! There's no time!
هيا بنا، لا وقت لدينا
Yeah!
حسنًا
Just how long will the rubber man last?
كم ثانية سيصمد فتى المطاط؟
Oh, so that's the game?
أهذه هي اللعبة إذًا؟
I see.
فهمت
You can have the fish.
لتتول أمر السمك
You can cut and trim the octopus.
وأما أنت فلتتول تشذيب الأخطبوط
Man... This is bad. I feel so weak...
هذا سيئ، قواي تخور
What do we do?! He's helpless down there!
ما العمل؟ ليس بوسعه مساعدة نفسه الآن
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
سيموت أخي الكبير لوفي
They can't even breathe underwater.
ليس بوسعهم حتى التنفس تحت الماء
Humans are utterly pitiful creatures!
البشر مخلوقات تثير الشفقة حقًّا
Bring it on!
تعال، أنا خصمك يا رجل الأخطبوط
Sure, I'm game!
لعبة، لعبة
I'll take care of you in five seconds!
سأنهي أمرك في خمس ثوان
No, three seconds!
بل ثلاث
Don't be in such a rush.
كفاكَ استعجالًا
It doesn't matter what you do! None of you are leaving here alive!
لا يتمتع أيٌّ منكم بأملٍ للنجاة
I-I'm dead meat!
!سـ-سأُقتل
Give us five seconds, Luffy! We'll beat them and save you!
سنتكفل بهم بخمس ثوان وبعدها سنأتي لإنقاذك يا لوفي
Octohachi Black!
قذيفة حبر هاتشي تاكوهاتشي بلاك
My hair! You bastard!
!شعري يا وغد
I'm gonna...
...سـ
forgive you.
أسامحك
It's just hair, so it'll grow back.
ما هو إلا شعر فسينمو ثانيةً
Roronoa Zoro!
!رورونوا زورو
You can't cut me because I have six hands.
ليس بوسعك قطعي لأنَّ لي ستة أيدٍ
Go ahead! Try to cut me!
هيا اقطعني إن استطعت
Octofreak!
!أيّها الرّجل الأخطبوط
Octo
!صد... هاتشي... الثلاثي... للسيوف
Ouch!
هذا مؤلم
I don't have time to play with you!
لا وقت لديّ لألهو معك
He throws me off my rhythm.
إنه يثير غيظي
Could he possibly...
...أيعقل أنه
Blink and you're dead!
انتبه وإلا فلن تعيش طويلًا
Fish shouldn't be fighting a cook!
ليس على السمك مهاجمة الطباخ
We're running out of time...
...الوقت ينفد منا... الوقت
Just drop dead already!
!أسرِع واسقط طريحًا
Octohachi Number...
هاتشي رقم تسعة تاكوهاتشي نمبر ناين
What are you doing?! Get down here already!
وما بهذا؟ انزل بسرعة
You damn octopus!
أيها الأخطبوط الخسيس
That octopest! He's just goofing around and stalling!
ذاك الأخطبوط اللّعين يتحرك بترنح وبطء
Still, if he goes in the water now, he'll be dragged to the bottom of the sea!
ولكن إن نزل إلى البحر الآن سيُسحب إلى قعره
But at this rate, Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
لكن على هذا الحال سيموت أخي الكبير لوفي
We've got to do something!
علينا فعل شيء
Yeah!
نعم
Wait!
انتظرا
– Ouch!
!آخ
How are you going to be any help with injuries like those?
ما الذي بوسعكما فعله في البحر بإصاباتكما البليغة؟
You can't do much when you're hurt like this.
لا تقدران على فعل الكثير بهذا
If you're talking about that rubber boy, I'll go rescue him.
إن كنتما تقصدان ذاك الشاب المطاطي فسأذهب وأنقذه
Y-You will?
حـ-حقًّا؟
Mr. Gen!
غين-سان
I'll go, too!
سأذهب معك
I'll go as well!
وأنا أيضًا
Me, too!
وحتى أنا
No! If too many of us go to rescue him, the fishmen are bound to notice.
كلا، إن ذهب كثيرٌ منّا لإنقاذه وتأخروا سيلاحظ البرمائيين ذلك
We'd just be making their job even harder!
وسيزيد ذلك الطين بلّة
Mr. Gen!
غين-سان
It'll be pointless if we end up interfering with their fight.
لن يكون هنالك مغزى إن تسبّبنا في عرقلة قتالهم
So I'll do it alone.
لذا سأذهب وحدي
Sorry... Thank you!
!اعذرنا... شكرًا لك
We'll leave it to you.
لتتول أمره، اعذرني ولكن أسرِع رجاءً
Wait!
انتظر
Mr. Gen, I'll go too.
سأذهب معك يا غين-سان
Nojiko, you're injured!
أنتِ مصابة يا نوجيكو
Those guys are fighting for my little sister!
إنهم يقاتلون من أجل أختي الصغيرة
Mr. Gen!
غين-سان
Okay. Come on!
حسنًا، تعالي معي
Let's hurry!
فلنسرع
Okay!
حسنًا
I'm sorry...
...معذرةً
If only we were a little stronger...
...لو كنَّا أقوى بقليل
Please... save Big Bro!
...أنقذا أخي الكبير... رجاءً
Roronoa Zoro! Do you mind if I ask you a question? You don't, right?
أتمانع إن سألتُكَ سؤال يا رورونوا زورو؟ لا تمانع، صح؟
I heard you use the three-sword style.
سمعتُ أنك تستخدم أسلوب الثلاثة سيوف فلمَ تستخدم سيفًا واحدًا حاليًا؟
One already seems like overkill for the likes of you!
سيف واحد يبدو كافٍ عليك
Sh-Shut up! I'm not taking this seriously!
ا-اخرس، إني لا أقاتل بجدية
Actually, there's a reason that a human swordsman could never defeat me.
في الواقع، ثمّة سبب لعجز السيافين البشر في هزيمتي
Wanna hear what it is? You do, don't you?
أتريد معرفته؟ تريد، صح؟
When you hear it, you'll be surprised, scared, blown away!
حينما تسمعه ستتفاجأ وتخاف وتُذهل
Dammit! I can't be in pain right now!
تبًّا، هذا ليس وقت التألم
I knew it. It's those wounds...
...كما توقعت، إنَّ الجراح
from your fight with Hawk Eye!
...التي تكبّدتها من قتالك مع عين الصقر
– Big Bro!
!أخي الكبير
Look! This is my true form!
انظر، هذه هي هيئتي الحق
Here comes Hachi, user of the six-sword style!
هاتشي مستخدم أسلوب الستة سيوف قادم
Hey! That's not when you're supposed to fall! Don't mock me!
على رسلك، لا يفترض بك أن تقع هكذا، لا تسخر مني
Ah! Big Bro!
!أخي الكبير
So he really was in pain!
إذًا فقد كان يتحمّل الألم
Yeah.
هذا أكيد
His injuries would kill a normal person or leave them bedridden for half a year!
كانت جراحه لتقتل رجلًا عاديًا أو لتتركه طريح الفراش نصف عامٍ
What?!
ماذا قلت؟
I knew something was off.
بدا لي الأمر غريبًا
Acting all nonchalant after a fight like that...
ادَّعى وكأنَّ لا شيء حدث من ذاك القتال
Is he an idiot or what?!
أهو أحمق أم نحو ذلك؟
I thought I told you not to blink.
ظننتني حذرتك أن تنتبه
I'm a 40th-degree black belt in Fishman Karate.
أنا حائز على أربعين درجة في كاراتيه البرمائيين
Wh-What?
مـ-ماذا؟
Someone went flying?!
أَعُصِف بأحدهم؟
B-Big Bro?!
أ-أخي الكبير؟
Big Bro Cook!
!أخي الكبير الطباخ
He's been taken care of, Arlong.
تكفَّلتُ بأمره يا أرلونغ-سان
What do we do with Roronoa Zoro?
ماذا نفعل برورونوا زورو؟
Just toss him in the sea. What weaklings... How boring!
!ارموا به في البحر، ما أضعفهم... ويا للملل
That's all?
أهذه النهاية؟
Geez, they sure wreaked some havoc.
على كلٍّ، تسبّبوا في أضرار كثيرة مع ذلك
It's no big deal.
ليس بالأمر الجلل
It'll take more than this to bring down Arlong Park.
لا يُمكن أن تُدمّر أرلونغ بارك بهذا المستوى من الأضرار
Indeed...
...فعلًا
How dare you, Roronoa Zoro!
كيف تجرؤ يا رورونوا زورو؟
You died from shock before I, the great swordsman, could attack you?!
هل مِتّ من الصدمة قبل أن أهاجمك أنا، السياف العظيم؟
History would've remembered you had you fallen to my six-sword style.
لخُلِّد اسمك في التاريخ لو مُتَّ بعد مواجهة أسلوبي للسيوف الستة
Well, struggle all you want or even flip the world on its head,
مهما كافحتم ولو انطبقت السماء مع الأرض
no human could ever lay a hand on me, the wielder of six swords!
يستحيل عليكم أيها البشر حتى أن تخدشوني أنا، مستخدم السيوف الستة
Stop it, Hachi.
كفاك يا هاتشي
I know how you feel, but we'll be in big trouble if you actually go on a rampage.
أفهم شعورك، ولكن إلم تتمالك نفسك سنقع في ورطة
Do you want to destroy Arlong Park?
أتنوي تدمير أرلونغ بارك؟
N-No. Sorry.
لـ-لا... اعذرني
I got a little too worked up.
...انفعلتُ كثيرًا
Don't get carried away.
لا تنجرف في حماستك
My bad, my bad.
معك حق، اعذرني
Six-sword style, huh? What a joke!
!أقلتَ أسلوب الستة سيوف؟ يا للسخف
Big Bro!
!أخي الكبير
Roronoa Zoro!
!رورونوا زورو
I'll tell you one thing, octopus.
لأخبرك بشيء أيها الأخطبوط
There's a man I need to meet.
أحتاج لقاء رجل
And until I see him again...
...وإلى أن ألقاه ثانيةً
even Death himself can't take my life!
لا يمكنني السماح ولو لحصاد الأرواح نفسه أن يحصد روحي
He's still alive!
ما زال حيًّا
Big Bro! Big Bro Cook!
أخي الكبير، أخي الكبير الطباخ
That fishman's punch was 40th-degree, huh?
كانت لكمة ذاك البرمائي من الدرجة الأربعين إذًا؟
Then all those kicks from the old fart must've been 400th-degree.
إذًا فركلات ذاك العجوز اللعين التي طالما تلقيتها من الدرجة الأربعمئة
This guy won't give up!
!ما أعنده